For tonight.
A couple of times.
I'll give you a minute from theстema.
First point.
Director Pink.
Second.
A couple of times.
rupees.
Not a score.
Five will lead.
Kegel to the next.
That's being kind of weird.
Six.
Another gift would be personal characters.
Perfect.
Common.
And I don't think that's notлом.
to speak in Chicago, in the manager of Miami City, Miami City, Miami City,
in the center.
Well, speaking to the council, they've regards to, they get out of the station,
when the matchman, they already kind of are shut down, and just do it.
They're not back for a lot of our business, but the many of them.
You know, they're looking at what we have, what we look at with this.
Maybe that huge impact that it's now looking at, you know, we have a matchman
in front of, that many of you come to the door and take their required.
You know, when we do all of those, for anybody to lie to them,
we often stand up and make some things like that.
They still take some visits now, you know, enter a choir that would have a great effect.
Well, that's, you know, so, it's something we want to look at, you know,
we looked at the numbers, understand that there's been 17, that's in Miami.
No one wanted to grab another, I agree that that's a tragic loss for us anyway.
And they've accepted that there's also a review of the numbers from the 29 teams season.
4,000 cases were a full 31 that we didn't have a matchman, and they've been,
I'm being stood up at the door and was still at the main camp.
You know, with this being far fewer numbers, I definitely want to see that council not get something
my face in effect.
It's not perfect.
I've visited as well as small businesses in the community around us.
Kind of around me and thank you guys.
Thanks, Paul.
Thank you.
I'm very old.
I'm Jim.
Thank you.
up with what Colin said, we really believe that if we implement and at this time, we already
have people that are apprehensive. We'll apply for our business. We'll apply for local economy.
I do not support the shadow down in businesses at this point. Based on that, I look back.
Again, I think there are 2,000 cases. And on the county, 2,361,
for this year or something that does, like we said, we don't wish that upon that anyway.
But the flu time residing in the reaction of the flu, and up to the heat cover about the
numbers that we are looking at now. So, I don't have anything to make. Thank you.
Good evening. Good evening. My name is Jay Cowan. Last time we were here at this mass mandate,
issue doctor calls her into the mass mandate is no different than a traffic stop sign. Really
doctor, that's your comparison with traffic. Traffic clause versus forcing someone to wear
something that has proven not to work, or actually unhealthy. Mandating businesses on what
they can and can do, destroying the economy, locking up the elderly so they have no family.
Please tell us doctor, whenever before an history has healthy people been tested in mass levels.
So, is this to inflate numbers? Test 20,000 and 200, positive and 20 sick. And then they say it's on the rise.
A friend of mine who has said to all of the money, how much money has been made off COVID tests,
how much money has been given by the government to hospitals for COVID, which remember is our money.
The other money is due to profession has been making laws for the so-called pandemic. How much money
of ours corporations making off this also do to online sales and small businesses crumbling?
Why are the doctors and scientists all over the world providing new claims? Do you know more than
they do? Or is it they don't have a socialist agenda? A nurse from the large hospital in spring
field, that the nurses union told the nurses not to sign any contracts in more than 12 weeks
because in June COVID-21 is coming, and they are running the man more money. Now how does this even possible?
Do they have a crystal ball? Why would something like this be said at all? Does it already stage?
We hear it's just mass. It's only six feet apart. It's only non-sensual businesses.
It's only a church, but you can still pray. It's only a farer restaurant. It's only a few months
which seems to keep changing. It's for the better good of everything. My 95%
a lot of was a nursing rehabilitation center, and she told me there were worse things than
dying, like isolation from family and friends.
Dr. I have been shot twice in almost paralyzed in a waist down. The doctor, I want you to
know anyone else, protect me from guns, either. Some years back I was with one of the larger
shares departments in the United States, and of course we were trying to be law enforcement
officers, but the Constitution was drilled in our heads over and over again.
Our department was concerned about everyone's constitutional rights. The sheriff there now
refuses to violate people's constitutional rights by enforcing mandates or shutdowns.
I pray this council and local law enforcement has the same integrity. Please
always remember you can vote yourself in the socialism, but you have to fight your way
out. Thank you for letting this be.
Thank you for letting me say that agenda, staff, recommends that we approve my mistake through the
letter. So, as well, but they will throw in my key numbers for the doctor in my policy.
Today, I don't know if you will know that, but they gave a personal advice. How about you, I mean, this is not the
health of the community. And I've never recalled some of those before, but I sure will take my
social security with them now, I think that's a good thing.
Naturally, there are 16,519,620 cases, the COVID-19 with 300,494 deaths. We have one of the poorest
responses in the world to COVID-19 pandemic, more resources than any other status.
Last Wednesday, 3,124 Americans died in the United States from COVID-19. By comparison, the
Biden never did this to the hands of Korea for the whole pandemic. It is around 2,000. Why?
Because they were back. It's part of their policies like this, both things that they do.
In Oklahoma, it was of the September 10th. There have been 225,463 cases of COVID-19 with
COVID-19 in the United States.
The 14 states without mass mandates for all of the average of cases per capita for the country.
In all of what county member cases of 2161, with an increase of 390 free cases since December 1st,
and 18.2% increase in 2 weeks.
There have been 25 deaths that break in our county's 1.2%.
That is from the health department.
So, you pay taxes on the home road, but you know we drive on the right side of the road.
Why is there this limitation on your personal freedom?
It is for the protection of health and safety of other and for everyone in drugs.
The mass mandate is also a minimal limitation for the protection and health of others as well as yourself.
The concern about it, for worse than the mass mandate, seems small compared to the boss of non-absorbed mass mandate.
Mass mandates have been shown to help decrease cases of COVID-19 even when they are not in the force.
This is the one to stay open, the one to force a mass query, currently or without any protection legally.
You know I am not the head of the snake here, they have this snake with the coronavirus virus.
And if you want to keep business open, then you need to take care of that problem.
I mean I got looked at me, I have really liked what I see.
I have gone out of the one time and I have thought I am a fatty of 12 of us.
I would love to do that again, but I don't go because I don't feel safe.
People who serve in my amode over mass.
People who are restaurants don't wear masks.
And I don't, this is not about shutting down many business.
It's about making people feel safe to go into business.
And right now people don't feel safe.
I've got a friend who goes to school in the norm and he says he has to do it.
He feels safe for a norm and it doesn't matter because the norm has a mask mandate.
And this is not, it's not, it's personal to me.
I told eight people in the afternoon that I told my team.
Eight people.
And so this Thanksgiving service that we predicted, it's kind of true.
It's going to give the worst worse.
And if you don't be certain of the poor Christmas, then the two or three weeks that are after Christmas, we're going to have an even more of you.
The hospitals, we haven't been.
Well, we don't have as extra people to staff.
And so if you go to the hospital and you can't get treated for your heart, that was what happens in major cities.
You stay at the ER for two days, waiting to get treated because there's no medicine.
There's no staff to take care of you in those beds.
So, in my view, for businesses that want to stay open, I would encourage math.
Now, if you have post-demand express this order, if you have hospital code, do you?
Those people should need to wear math, but they need to stay six feet apart from everybody.
You know, those are the things that you've had now, or people that would think they're with the things.
And now, how can you say that?
So, the first vaccines have been released, and hopefully, we're planning on getting it on Friday for healthcare workers.
That's a wonderful thing.
A bit of vaccine comes out in two weeks, and then there's two more that come out from different companies in January.
Well, if the vaccination goes as low as you plan, by probably by late spring or December, we'll be back to normal.
We won't be wearing that.
So, there's good news on the rise, but if between now and then, we have to do some work.
And by any time, we're able to offer the current therapist for COVID-19, including the Revisibir,
on the last two weeks, we've been offering Bands of Meta-Man therapy, which is the Honorable Anne-Vyre, the President Trump, the United States, because this medicine that we only use from people are not in the hospital.
It only works to prevent the replication or the vision of the virus.
It does not work after you get to the plant for a day.
But we've given a lot of, I would say, in view of more institutions of this, the company offers the medicine for free by the family.
And the insurance phase for the therapy and the future.
It's a great thing, it's finally something I can offer to people when they call us and I call them and tell them how to do it.
I can say, you know, we can do this and they keep you on the hospital.
It's a win-win thing, because it takes the pressure on the hospital and pays it to the United States.
Yes, the third of the United States needs to remember the hospital of the United States.
So, our national failure response to the coronavirus pandemic started, but the federal government decided a lot to take responsibility.
And let the individual state responsible for the health crisis.
In some states like ours, state leaders failed to take responsibility to ask you to do this to tell you to take responsibility.
Since we've been put down to the United States, the health hazard approach has been a public health nightmare.
What they're asking is in the city council, consider a vast mandate to provide for the citizens of Miami, the same protection you're providing for the importance of the city council.
time is at the end of it, really Christmas is going to be another huge surge at two weeks
after it. I don't make any extra money off this. I'm not a socialist. I don't like
not the idea to keep it. You know, I come from a family, you know, I was burdened in this
of all business. So for me, I want those people to succeed and I want to do everything we can.
I don't think we're going to step down for us, but I think the people who serve the only
person have. I don't think we don't set down our agencies, so I think people that are certainly
with people who are asking the people that don't want to wear a mask, that's fine. There's a lot
of different ways to do this. You don't have to make it, you know, I don't want to set down any
business. But I'm going to tell you this, that the coronavirus is going to cause cold damage to
business than any mask. So, you have any questions at all? I don't think I can make that.
I don't think I can make that. I don't think I can make that. If you don't set it around after you
don't do that. Thank you, Mark. Thank you.
Number 13, allow the council to authorize the naming of the solid-licing money to J.C.
give the grant to the council. I don't think I can.
On September 30th, Ms. Jean, we lost one more city employees. J.C. Kennedy, who worked with the solid-licing
government who was a driver collector of three, which is the top tier of the information
of the department. We went from one to two to three. J.C. and then completed the
grant for the council to log in on us in 2,000 to 8, 30,500 sold, the act of work for the day
that can be asked to want again a few hours a week. So, his mother and a candidate is written
the letter to the title in the City Manager asking if the council would approve naming the
that leads me into solid waste,
James Kennedy wanted to just be kind of enlightened.
And it is not a road.
So Tyler would have been able to just say,
give you a approval, but felt more comfortable
coming before the council asking for that historical
documentation of why it was made back to prove that the slime
will look similar to a spree slime,
that will be this black and white slime,
$100 dollars, and then it will be put up on the existing
hole where this already failed.
The staff in this hallway waste department is 100%
of what I guess, all of this went into come and see me.
more time than the employees' other exposure, but they do want their place to be heard that they
need more than 100% of the time. So we're asking them to help some of that.
I think it's great, great, great. Great that one of that question. I give her a question,
you know, I'd like you to split her son for a moment or I don't know.
And one thing if you do take C.A. you let go of cars. And every time you saw on the other
car, so I know we've had this vote too on the employees up there. They said probably have to be
certain more cars on that line than J.C. did because he worked on cars. I also want to mention,
I want to thank their firm, there was an employer or street department that worked with J.C.
in some ways for quite a few years. They were very, very good friends. And he was taught a really nice
bit that they're putting out of this all the way to facility also on J.C.
in some ways.
I'd like to be approved. I have 14 and 15 will be taken to the back room. For 16,
election resolution, C.C. 2020-26, calling for work, providing and worrying in non-partisan
their election, because they might have a cat about what state will allow them to do, they
will allow them to look at the purpose of electing state council members for four or three
top-less and who are four of the top teams.
Are you looking at the top?
Well, it's nine.
15 discussion in the bottom of the building, I think the dollar general store, the top-less boundary,
the top-less boundary of the city limits, the city of Egypt.
First of all, you've been in the job. Talk to us about that.
I think, I'll probably need upon the presents, especially this, that Mr. Brune from the
group, the unit right, the room health room group, is doing construction, is here in the
questions in the garages.
Also, we have with us Mr. Mr. Mr. Goodrich, who are the parties involved with the good-rich
management trust. This is a very, very, very complicated mess.
It started that in the late 50s when the city acquired the whole railroad of the railway that
went from the city all the way down to Grand Light.
And the reason the city acquired the cat.
In the event, the Rick and I do not prefer to get our lunch time ever to buy that,
and to animate it or whatever, for we no longer get our water from there, this was to give us the opportunity to bring water
from the rain light, through a height of water, the water that it became necessary.
We cannot find this point, we have not been able to find our records in the birth of that,
which seems to be a common problem, we have with all the boxes and boxes of documents.
We have been able to come up with some of the permanent documents that actually reflect this particular personal plan.
And to try and make a long story short, the Rick and I agree now owns the parcel of plan that is immediately at the intersection.
And I'm assuming everybody puts a little problem.
Because of various problems with that real estate that they are needing to acquire the additional section of plan a little bit to the east of the land that they need to plot.
That plan that they need to acquire is all of the cities.
Basically, the city had needed all the land along this right away, back to the property owners, but reserved the pipeline of easements on it.
If everything is necessary for us to put that pipeline in, or whatever reason, we don't know at this point time.
If there was a need from the city, this particular partial land is very not possible.
And so we think it was either the deed was not then either the error, or it was then just not lost.
But it very not possible.
The differences are the numbers of the property that this, if the deed had been filed with the deed, if the property was back to the end.
Their correct message of interest nonetheless went ahead and deeded the easement of the plan away to the city.
So part of what should have happened is that it's not all.
There's now a problem for the root group and it's also a problem.
So what we're proposing, and we have, I know it's very difficult to see that from here.
But what we're proposing, if this is what she wants to do, is to be back to the future
and to that property, we should have been back to their credit centers in the membership of the interest
in the 1950s and 60s, reserving the city's right away.
And the differences to be, was, of course, that the group group means,
or of their community development.
And then, after all that, what's in the form of city, is that the group group within the region,
the city, the city, the national land where the stores in the city ranks.
Oh, no!
They didn't follow all that.
You'd like to try to answer the questions that you may have.
Right now, all this changed, but some months since we first started working on it,
it got a little bit more complicated, legally, but between the attorneys that are involved
and all of that, this is the way you want to get the results we could get results.
And so again, both of the other parties here, we're going to go through some of those with them also.
So originally, just a couple of months, it didn't even happen to them.
It shouldn't have been the impact of the Williams who owned the property before, or it could be the result.
So what do you mean?
We're cleaning up the mass, we're solving the problem for us, we're solving the problem,
we're going to get rid of the issues we've solved in the problem.
I'm sorry if they didn't be a damn it.
The way we're solving the problem for us is that there was a miles of space.
So we still have these with do there, just be aware.
So we were still having these, now, the question has been raised, whether or not the city is actually abandoned,
that needs to be there at some point in time.
Like I say, we don't know that right now.
You know, hopefully we will find the rest of the records that we can't find the records that we're meeting.
We'll have to do that here.
Which a lot of work is going to be done on the city's part, as to what ultimately needs to be done.
But this takes care of the immediate problem for these parties to put the city.
So what the proposal is right now is for you all to just decide whether this is the way you want to approach it.
What we need to do.
because they're not more complicated since we first started this.
We'll prepare between the training, we'll prepare an agreement to visit that.
We'll prepare the D from the city to the good rich, deadly trust.
Between the good rich is the good group, they'll take care of their transaction.
And then that takes care of everything, for right now, and after the construction,
we'll finish the agreement with the annexation, which we'll all be set out in the city.
We'll still have these, but we'll still have these.
We'll still have these, we'll need the property subject to the training that these will be brought by the way.
I don't know if that's sort of a...
Well, they might have to sit and utility.
But yes, they're not.
We mentioned that we have to, and it doesn't affect its best for the treatment.
Well, what is that present in the future?
Do you find it?
Is there anything to do with it?
If we find that the city is otherwise totally abandoned this season, all the way down to the left,
then there's no point in our remaining any piece on whatsoever of this particular piece of property to the bottom of that.
So we can claim that at that point it's very easy thing to do.
We just don't know right now everything that the city has been going back to the late 1950s,
and we're just part of it because we can't buy our orders.
And all this that has been looking for and are asked to score each decision.
It's our opinion, it's important for me.
But I think the important thing to keep the name of that name,
is that we should definitely keep the opposite of that name, man.
Well, if we haven't otherwise got rid of all the rest of it,
then we're still maintaining this part of it.
This part is obviously very important because it's the first,
very first section of the easement outside of the city limits.
If we were to abandon that right now, it doesn't matter what we've done there.
It helps, it's all meetings.
But if we abandon everything else, then there's no reason why we should keep this for you.
Don't worry about that.
We're asking for your going dance, so we can clear all the work and all the percentage of you
in the next meeting, which if we don't develop any other problems,
I would say that we should just go off the consent agenda.
along with the other things that are on top of the first thing.
But the point is, is we need guidance from the right now.
Is this the way you want us to try to resolve this issue?
We need to talk some talking about it.
They don't know what the alternative would be anyway,
honestly, what the alternative is.
We do not think the good rich is probably
at a loss to against the highly insurance company
that they got on insurance floor.
And the regroup is really nice enough on trying to finish their construction.
So it's bigger consequences for the other parties
than it is for us, that our benefit is the annexation
that you're beginning to have.
I'm very keen to have a new business.
I've never seen it.
My team is staff reports.
I want to thank the local community of excellence.
They've got a 100 of them.
They've got a lot of problems and cheap bill falls.
And they don't raise 180 gallons of hands at that time
to try a part of the day.
They've never do them.
And I'm so excited that you deserve to do them.
I'm 21.
In terms of the managers, you can get you.
It's our third thing.
The first one is the main trades, maybe a long time.
We've been sitting in the light.
We've been out here today.
I'm sorting out the control box that's
to even collect the stuff.
We have to have a nice, pretty bright.
The new life that our community intersects.
We have design then.
To be able to hang the old time prisoners both on.
That was previously something that we worked very hard with.
They actually, um, Sean, who did that.
It was actually the first one in the light manufacturing.
That's actually the time.
Oh.
We didn't have another one.
So there's a greater number on everything.
So it's not a special bill.
It just makes it easier.
It makes it easier.
It makes it easier for the other.
So the intersection will build a game.
You'll have a person involved.
I mean, we can try to get through the main trades.
So we're not over here.
If you will always want to do that.
I love Christmas stuff.
So I'm excited about that.
I'm next thing is the one I've been doing here in Minnesota planning to do it right now.
And I think it's a very back-to-date in the river tracks.
And the last one is, I'd like to say thank you for the opportunity to be there.
And this is my opportunity to put a special need.
So I'd like to thank the council for the opportunity to do this.
I'd like to thank staff.
You're very hard when you can see the community.
I appreciate that very much.
I appreciate the opportunity to do this very hard.
I like to thank my community a lot.
To a lot of time on my family and my young daughter who is on scholarship that very much.
I mean I think we have three years of grant to be a manager.
So I'm happy to get one to the.
I'm seeing it at the time of four.
I'm excited about that.
And I'm up to the opening here in the United States.
Thank you.
I'm going to talk to you.
You should go over that week for I did.
And even if you really don't get a lot, I may not.
My transmission is going to be so appreciative.
And I'm going to do the journey.
I'm going to talk to you.